JACQUELINE DI CAMILLO

For this position, you're seeking a qualified senior professional with some key ingredients: senior management, visionary, liaison, decision-making, result orientation, global vision working with diverse cultures, using influence rather than authority to impact/change business and strategic orientation. Am I right?

First, I possess in-depth experience as a Senior Executive. Managing and overseeing complex, diverse and large-scale operations (HR, Healthcare, Education, Administration, IT, Audit and Strategy) in a multicultural environment (Americas, Africa, Asia, Middle East and Europe). Using an excellent interpersonal, clear communication, leadership and negotiation skills to deliver complex solutions in multiple locations (globally). I guide and assist the institution to better understand how to achieve top-quality service. I have 30 years of experience not just to delivery what was expected but to exceed expectations working the second mille as a visionary. My management style is a participatory one when I lead by example rather than by authorities. Lead a team of more than 500 people and budget of \$700MM.

Second, you're seeking a candidate with intricate knowledge of interaction with all levels in the institution, as well as, a lead able to create the standards, frameworks and procedures, as well as, to work in reengineering of the process according with the global vision of the institution but in the meantime work together with the senior lever team to support the business plan.

By the end, the most important for me is to know if your institution is really looking for senior executive, able to manage not just IT but Strategic business change and transformation of an organization on global basis. If yes, I am more than able to discuss my qualifications further, or to answer questions, please contact me.

I look forward to discussing this opportunity with you.

Thanks for giving my request your consideration.

Sincerely,

Jacqueline Di Camillo

Summary

System engineer with 30 years of exeperience as a Senior IT executive in multinational companies.

Senior management – Visionary – Liaison – Decision-making – Result orientation –

Flexible Solutions – Strategic orientarion – Global experience.

~ Lead international teams of up to 500 and anunal operating budget of U\$700MM ~

JACQUELINE DI CAMILLO

CIO

EDUCATION

LANGUAGE

PORTUGUESE

ENGLISH

SPANISH

FRENCH

ITALIAN

CITIZENSHIP

BRAZILIAN & ITALIAN

1990 - 1993

Brazil

BACHELOR OF SYSTEM ENGINEER



S jdicamillo

dicamilloj@hotmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/dicamillo

EXPERIENCE

CHIEF TECHNOLOGY OFFICER - PRO MUJER

2015 - 2016

Leadership and overall direction of IT. Align technology infraestructura with organizatonal strategy and busines processes. Advise team members on policies and procedures, technical problems, priorities and methods. Took the business of IT to the next level through improve budgeting, licenses, contracts and staff management, as well as strategic directions for critical core banking system, health and technology system. Direct report to CEO.

VICE PRESIDENT OF TECHNOLOGY & STRATEGY – ACCION INTERNATIONAL

2008 - 2014

Enforce fiscal accountability for IT business-wide, while driving stratgey and ensuing that the organization's mission is reflected in agile decision-making surrounding the delivery of key systems, sites and services. Measusures and performance metrics are crucial for greater transparency, sucess visibility and cost containment in managing staff, equipment, costs, purchasing and operations as the organization enters a new growth phase. Direct report to COO.

SENIOR INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY HEAD - BANK OF AMERICA / BANKBOSTON

2003 - 2007

Head of IT for a global finance system merger rollout. Manage project design, execution, staffing, architecture, training, support, policies, procedurses, documentaion, guidance, mapping process and proposal for changes to day-by-day busines process, capacity plan for 9 multi-sites of operations. Direct report to CFO.

MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEM MANAGER - ACNIELSEN (Europe & Latin America)

1996 - 2002

Provide strategic and tatical internal systems development effots and assures consistency with corporate requeriments and business objetives. Manage the unification of the European MIS and design/implementation of the EURO currency conversion plan. Direct report to CFO.

TECHNICAL LIASSION MANAGER, CITIBANK 1991 – 1995 SYSTEM ANALYST, SANTANDER BANK 1986 - 1990

EXPAT

United States of America, Ghana,

Belgium, Mexico

DISTINCTIVE FIT AND VALUE

| Strategic IT Vision | Governance / Policy | IT Transformation |
|-----------------------------|------------------------------|---------------------------|
| Cloud Environment | Nonprofit | Operational Efficiency |
| Project & Change Management | Budget Mgt / Cost Reductions | Organizational Redesign |
| Emerging Technologies | Global Technology Deployment | Cultural Diversity Issues |
| App. Developmnet Issues | ERP / CRM / BI Experience | Core Banking Systems |
| C-Level / Board Reporting | Data Analysis / Security | Vendor / Contract Mgt. |